Speed on!
There it is!
Take the road!
Stop there!
Stop, I said!
I'm not a wild boar.
I am your emperor Frederick of Hohenstaufen.
Are You "Barbarossa"?
Will I be called like this.
Who are you?
My name is Alberto da Giussano.
Son of Giovanni, wrought from Milan.
Well, smith...
Take this dagger.
It will serve you when you grow up.
The Emperor is suit!
I do not know whether it is wise.
Hildegard of Bingen is an accomplished
seamstress who can see through people.
As a 5 year old she could describe
an unborn calf to the letter.
They make their own music.
Calf had died inside the uterus.
Why have you come here?
My hosts are here to ask for your advice.
He is getting married tomorrow and was wondering...
The wedding is blessed.
Innocence tree is not mature yet,
but the roots are strong.
She will bear fruit.
Come closer...
They...
Who is pretending to be king among kings.
Is it written in my fate.
I have to reunite the empire?
Listen to what I say, Frederick of Swabia ...
Their name will be remembered for centuries.
But beware...
Beware of the water.
Beware of the sword.
With the sword comes defeat.
With water comes death.
Beware of the water.
Here comes the future empress.
I hope she makes my cousin
happier than his first wife.
She could not endure his love
or give him children.
We hope everyone.
His Majesty has been waiting
for an heir long enough.
He must wait a while yet.
He can console himself with the fact
that Beatrix comes with all Burgundy.
- Who is it that Eugenie?
- Henry of Saxony.
He is the emperor's cousin.
He is called the "Lion".
Leo Henry...
She is prettier than the first.
- She's only a child!
- I did not know she was so young.
She should at least be able to have babies.
The French girl seems promising.
She apparently can even read.
My dad will kill me.
- You're wet. What have you done?
- I will not talk about it.
- Evandro would leave without you.
- Sorry, Dad.
- We must reach the river before dusk.
- Sorry, Evandro.
Join them!
- Lodi citizens still sleeping.
- It's probably good.
Did you hear that?
- Hurry, Give me them!
- Looking at it!
How many fine products.
Check them.
What do you want?
We are not on your land.
Not right now, but they passed it before.
It should I pay for.
On them!
Take it, then I take the other.
Hurry, Alberto!
Does he know you love him?
Of course not.
Rainero since Giussano
is too shy and a bit stupid ...
If he waits too long,
the others swarm about you.
And you?
Nobody wants me, but it's alright.
I can not love anyone other than him.
Alberto!
You too compassionate end!
Tessa!
Milanese, exploiting every chance
to show their superiority.
We find this disturbing, your majesty.
That's why we've come.
The city of Lodi has always
been your majesty faith.
Now it needs the emperor's help.
Milanese is being arrogant.
It is time to remind them of
how sharply the Emperor's sword.
We can go south already in two weeks.
No!
We do not go on the attack yet.
If the North within you...
They are the mightiest in Europe.
I write a letter and
advises them to calm down.
I shall deliver it.
The Emperor warns you against attacking Lodi.
Otherwise, Milan banned.
Gherardo!
Here you have our answer.
They have gone too far.
It's going to regret you.
- What have you done?
- Wait, Rainald.
Your Excellency!
What should we do now?
Put together an army.
We go on the attack against Lodi.
My goodness...
Alberto...
Alberto da Giussano...
Smith Sun
It was not part of our agreement, did it?
We succeeded, Alberto!
Lodi would pay for his insolence.
- Are you already back?
- Do you fool? You've slept in 4 days.
We defeated Lodi.
They have had to pay.
- Come on, we celebrate it out there.
- Come on!
They are ready.
They had no choice, your grace.
They seem to force me to go to war,
though I will have peace.
I know, but you must go to Italy.
Milanese want autonomy,
but the dream of the great empire.
Crush them.
Hugs Milan, your grace!
A prophecy came to my ear
just before we married.
It was about a sword and water.
The sword came with defeat,
and the waters of death.
Was it a prophecy or witchcraft?
I also have a prophecy for you.
As an queen I predict that
you will triumph in Italy.
In the properties of your wife,
I predict that you will miss me.
The dogs are restless.
afraid of thunder.
It is not thunder, they are afraid.
There is someone out there.
My goodness, where did you fear me!
What are you doing out in this weather?
I will talk to you. In private.
- I listen.
- I'm going north toward Barbarossa.
I knew already.
Yes, but the thing is...
I have two women in the house,
who are you looking for?
I will ask Tessa hand.
Tessa...
Tessa is married mature, so this
may well be the start of something good.
- Will you talk to her?
- Yes. I argue your wishes.
- I have planned it all.
- It's understood.
I return.
Now we finally advanced.
They must conquer this part
if you intend to reach Sicily.
Rome is located right in the middle.
This will not be easy.
Rome is weakened.
Wait some time yet.
How long then?
The stubborn Englishman,
Pope Hadrian IV, is soon dead.
His successor is said to be
considerably more docile.
They will soon sit on the throne
that belonged to Charlemagne.
We continue.
I got you!
Siniscalco Barozzi came home
to us yesterday evening.
- He asked for my sister Tessa's hand.
- Barozzi is a creep.
He is never going to marry my sister.
How can you know?
I can feel it.
So is it true what they say.
That you are a kind of witch.
Wait...
Wait!
I got something for you.
With this vagina,
I take care of you the rest of my life.
With dagger I defend you with my life.
What?
What's wrong?
Eleonora...Do you sleep?
No.
I'll show you something.
Look here...
- Has he finally decided?
- Rainero has given me his promise.
Do not say anything to Dad.
He feels that Siniscalco Barozzi
is a suitable candidate.
He may be consulted.
It is not him who is forced
to share a bed with Barozzi.
Listen to your heart, Tessa.
What you do.
Sleep now! There is also a tomorrow.
My heart has already decided.
So this is how it should be.
My goodness!
They can go into.
I have come to speak to the emperor.
They must be content with talking to me.
I think Milan and hollow cupboard.
- Milano has a short memory.
- Now I'm not quite.
They were present when the
Milanese Officers stomped on the letter.
I was humbled and humiliated by your rabble.
I am here to apologize.
Our conversation is over.
Greet your consuls and
say that the emperor comes...
And it is no courtesy visit.
Many nobles of Milan is at the Emperor's side.
They have done what they can, Barozzi.
It stays here.
It's true. I'm afraid.
I've even seen what the German army can inflict.
Their tent covered the entire field.
They had so many war machines...
That they would not even fit on our square!
I implore you...
To capitulate.
- Capitulate!
- No, we must fight!
Barbarossa's army is here soon.
Milan's day can be counted on one hand.
Every time we come here,
they build a new, stronger bridge for us.
Verona people respect tradition.
When the German king comes,
they are obliged to build a bridge.
We respect them for that.
Your Majesty!
What is it going?
Beware of tree trunks!
Stop!
Tie the rope tight!
It's a trap!
Help him up!
No, your majesty!
Think of the prophecy of water and death.
Help emperor!
Take the rope!
He is under water! Dive!
No...
Find him!
Dive!
No...My goodness!
Give me your hand!
What I have done is very serious.
In and Milan have gone against the Empire.
I have robbed many German soldiers.
I have not respected the custom,
which has saved Verona past.
How can it be?
It is an important day,
and there is one thing I must know.
One can only betray his emperor once.
I'm just so cruel...
God is good.
Alberto!
Barbarossa has crushed Brescia!
More than one thousand have died.
How do you know?
Have you had a revelation again?
What do you want us to do?
Should we let the Germans win?
It would make no difference.
We are and remain slaves.
We will not be slaves anymore.
- They have already lost this war.
- Enough is enough!
Our duty is to defend our city...
And your duty is to sit home
and wait for your man!
If you then have one.
- Do not use this to her again.
- Alberto!
Enough is enough.
There they are.
Wonderful.
How many cities, we must crush
before they come to their senses?
Just one more. We crushes Milan.
So will other cities follow
their shepherd like frightened sheep.
Milan, Milan, Milan...
Parma greet the Emperor!
Cremona greet the Emperor!
Padua greet the Emperor!
Ferrara greet the Emperor!
What burns the most of?
Being able to fight for the empire ...
Or to contribute to Milan's downfall?
They are sheep Rainald.
They do not think.
They just need to obey the emperor.
- Did you hear that?
- It sounded like thunder.
It is not thunder. It sounds like...
Look over there!
Barbarossa!
Barbarossa! Barbarossa!
Hurry!
It is the largest army, I've seen.
Come, Alberto.
Alberto!
Hurry, Alberto!
Hurry!
What?
Do not let them fight.
I saw the arrows...
You must prevent it!
The Germans are out there.
There are arrows everywhere.
- What are you talking about?
- It was not German arrows.
We are ready as soon as the sun rises.
- How many war machines do we have?
- About a hundred.
The tower is unfortunately too far away.
- Can we not go further?
- No, your majesty.
Milanese has built a moat around the city.
Machines can not come closer...
Wise move. Do you have any suggestions?
I think we should concentrate
on crossbows masons...
While we fill the moat with earth.
Milanese feel safe within the city walls.
They must be detained there,
and we block all exits.
They are going to starve,
and if they do not give up...
Is the city their tomb.
Press!
Put them in place!
- They are preparing an attack!
- Take cover!
Fire!
Take cover!
Throw the barrels down!
Roll the drums!
They throw barrels into the water.
They try to get closer to the tower!
Hurry!
Fire!
Do not let them rest.
We deprive them of all food and rest.
They become more and more debilitated.
Guy and leave again!
Take cover! Hurry!
Hurry, faster!
Against the wall! Speed on!
Grab!
Take cover!
Races...Fast!
Hither!
Stop!
Download some rock! Hurry!
50 meters from the wall!
Are you ready?
Fire!
We need one volunteer per family
can go and get food.
Who goes?
You, you...
Yes.
I saw no young Rainero
since Giussano his arm up.
Let him alone, Barozzi.
His brother Otto and I'm here.
- Choose one of us instead.
- Well...
Since your brother apparently
did not feel like I should go instead.
No!
No one should say Rainero
since Giussano was scared.
One per family, he said.
We will not stop a young man
to show how brave he is.
Come near Sant 'Ambrogio in half an hour.
Get your weapons.
You decide not to me!
Do not tell me what I should do.
Close the gate!
Be careful.
Tessa...They should be back now.
I fear the worst.
I pray that there has them something.
Whatever happens,
I will always take care of you.
- You're not alone.
- Do not touch me!
My heart belongs Rainero
since Giussano forever.
If he does not come back,
I would rather die than live with you.
Can you hear it?
The Germans have stopped shooting.
Hurry! The Germans attack!
Tessa!
Germans go on the attack.
They are approaching!
- Can not you see them?
- They have stretched them onto the tower.
What are you waiting for? Shoot!
Don't mind us! Shoot!
- What should we do, Alberto?
- Shoot, before it's too late!
No, Barozzi!
We can not kill our own!
- Alberto!
- I do not know!
What is it that sits on the tower?
No. Do not look!
Get them out of here!
Don't do it!
I ask you so amicably.
- Do not!
- We can't shoot our own!
No, Alberto!
I'll shoot!
Shoot! Don't mind us!
- No, Alberto!
- Do not look.
Shoot!
No, I'm asking ...
- Don't shoot!
- Shoot!
Father!
- We must take cover.
- Hurry!
Retreat!
They retire.
- How could you!
- Take her away!
Poor baby ...
Antonia, I beg you.
The coast is clear.
- I killed my brother Otto.
- Take it easy.
It was not your fault.
Forgive me.
I killed Otto!
Father...Feel this knife.
Feel it.
I kill the man who killed my brothers.
I put the knife in his heart.
- Alberto!
- Leave me in peace.
Sufficiently many women
have lost their husbands.
- I just need to inspect the walls.
- I know where you're going.
I can see in your eyes where you're headed.
Don't talk about women who have lost
their husbands. My brothers are dead!
I tried to stop you.
Why did you?
I tried to protect you.
Is this how you protect the people?
By denying their feelings?
- You do not understand.
- I know what I feel.
If you love me...
If you love me, do not leave me.
Leave me alone.
- Where did you get hold of the dagger?
- They gave it to me.
It is some time ago.
You are smith Sun
How dare you come here?
You must pay with your life.
I'm not afraid.
There are hundreds of others
who are prepared to implement this.
Your city is consumed within a few days.
Many more will die before then.
I remember you.
I have thought much of you
since you saved my life...
And took a seat in my destiny.
I ought to summon the guards...
But I will not.
I let you go.
Their days are numbered, old king.
Damn you.
- Alberto!
- Father...
- Where are your daughters?
- I can not tell.
I promised Eleonora not telling
where she was going.
And especially not to you, Alberto.
The Germans are here!
Who has opened the door?
Move you!
- There has been shed enough blood.
- Guitelmo!
- Tessa was not home.
- Beware, Siniscalco Barozzi!
Even the darkest dogs can be seen
in the torches glow.
This dog has teeth.
Before the farmers away.
Before them away!
- Come on!
- I kill you!
I kill you, whether it's
the last thing I do.
Milan has fallen.
Road to Sicily lies open.
Soon Charlemagne's empire yours.
How goes it for those
who rebel against Caesar.
I order that Milan will be
razed to the ground.
None of the towers must stand upright.
I told everyone milan cleaners
to leave the city before sunset.
Spread you, so nobody can call
themselves milan cleaners.
The name Milan should be
removed from all maps.
No.
I will always be by your side.
It is the custom here in Burgundy.
Can you see that he has a dagger on him?
An armed emperor at his coronation...
It is quite incredible.
With a crown and a dagger
you can get very far.
Not least when the Pope,
who crowns Barbarossa is elected by himself.
Barbarossa! Barbarossa!
We must revive Rome's heyday.
They have Rome on their feet
and soon the entire South.
- Guard!
- Yes, Your Majesty.
A man has collapsed.
Check what it is about.
- It's the plague, your majesty.
- My goodness!
We ride from here!
Move you!
Good evening.
For God's sake, Lorenzo!
Look what has happened.
We have to meet in secret as outlaws.
Our people are starving...
And we have to endure the imperial guards spot.
They have increased taxes on the crops again!
We must do something!
Ro!
It is pointless to wrangle.
- What is happening?
- They hold a secret meeting.
Milan nobility.
We were starving and had to leave Milan
and go their separate ways.
- Who is it?
- Negro and dell'Orto.
Barbarossa has robbed us all.
Our homes, our work, our pride and dignity.
We must strike back!
- We must rebuild the city.
- How could that be?
I'm just tired faces that don't have
the energy to fight anymore.
Barbarossa becomes stronger
with every passing day.
- He is the ruler of Milan.
- He is right in!
- Lombardy people have accepted it.
- Lower the swords!
He is with us.
We can triumph over him...
If we stand united.
Listen to what I have to say.
I can still see how Milan raseres...
And the people's eyes when
they are forced to leave their homes.
I feel the anger and consternation
from Barbarossa allies.
Lombardy fought against Milan and then regret.
They understood that it was our invited disputes...
Which made us into slaves under Caesar.
- Milan would still...
- It's not true!
Imagine how strong we could be together!
Think what effect our swords would be capturing.
You are noble men...
I must do what is right.
I'm with you, Alberto.
- Whatever you want to do.
- Lorenzo...
The meeting is over. Now we go!
That's me.
We had a meeting at the monastery again.
We have still not decided.
Alberto...
- Do you live here alone?
- What does he do here?
- Alberto...
- Where is your sister...Tessa?
- Tessa is dead.
- Is it true?
Is it true?
What happened?
Tessa is no longer with us.
It's no use talking about it.
I ask for your permission
to take your daughter away.
- She can not stay here alone.
- I feel good here.
You have my permission.
- Why did you leave me?
- You did me no harm.
I was scared and angry.
Sorry.
You treated me like an anybody.
- Antonia!
- Eleonora!
Eleonora!
Antonia!
Where am I glad to see you!
You came back!
Where is it nice to see you!
How nice that you're here.
Emperor's men!
Take them into.
- They know why we have come.
- The bastards!
A third of the crop belongs to Caesar.
Naturally, your excellency.
- What have you there?
- It is our forge.
So great a barn into a blacksmith?
This I doubt.
Emperor's men treat us like animals...
And we give them permission.
It must have an end now.
We want our freedom.
Freedom.
Do you understand what I mean?
We are looking for more young men...
Who are prepared to die for freedom.
We form an army.
Help me keep it.
It should be our symbol.
An iron ring.
It must unite us all.
It is a sign from God!
Hurry!
Hundreds have died in the epidemic!
- We live in the least.
- They should get out of here!
It is bad that the plague
breaks out at your coronation.
Do not be silly.
That's because just the heat.
She interrupted the meeting!
It's incredible!
Everyone says that, unfortunately,
it is a sign from God.
The coronation was blasphemous and
that Pope Alexander, God's support.
Stop!
She interrupted him!
God is on your side, Fredrik.
He wants you to become
ruler of the whole earth.
Continue south.
They can not give up now.
No, everyone is afraid of the plague,
and we are losing control.
- We should leave the pestilential town.
- He is right.
Excellent...
Tell everyone that we're leaving.
We're going home.
That was all.
Begin preparations for our departure.
Where is that many poor, Alberto?
Who will want them?
There are not so many fingers here.
Well, my friend.
There are many fingers as rings careful.
I've thought about it for many years.
Emperor's men exploit fear and death...
To divide us up and take control.
Everyone is scared.
If we could avail ourselves of the fear...
And get it to unite us...
We would be invincible.
What have we to lose? Death?
Death...
Death to the Emperor's men!
We can call ourselves the death company.
- Death's company?
- It's a good suggestion.
- Death's company!
- Death in the name of freedom.
Death in the name of freedom!
Death and Freedom, my friend.
You get into trouble someday.
There you can just watch!
Otho! Do you remember me?
Lorenzo! What are you doing here?
Are you tired of all the Christmas games?
It does not.
I already have too much to do.
It is filled up in prison.
Nobody will notice anything.
They were two.
No, they killed almost
two of the Emperor's men.
- Take the other two.
- No, I want those two.
Who is it?
Who am I?
We are tired of being harmed.
- And?
- Break it over.
Also it.
Milan has been so humiliated
that it is becoming unbearable.
Brescia will help you
against the emperor...
And to rebuild Milan.
Mantua 'inhabitants will not
just look at...
But you know what the Emperor would reply.
He is right. The threat of
retaliation will scare people.
How will the Lodi and Pavia act?
We stick together.
We stand united the Lombard states.
We are not waiting Barbarossa retaliation.
An army is invincible,
with a strong heart.
Not least a wounded heart.
Ride back to your cities...
And ask young people whether they
want to continue living that way.
You know what they will answer?
- Better dead than slave.
Death company from Milan.
- Bergamo!
- Brescia!
Mantua!
Barbarossa trampling on our soil.
It belonged to us,
so long as we can remember.
We, the soldiers in death company,
vows to take our country back.
We are fighting against the emperor
and never shows the enemy back.
All towns must stand united
to defend the principal that we have.
Our freedom.
Our freedom! Freedom!
Freedom!
There you are!
You too compassionate end, Eleonora!
Where am I happy!
Where is it nice to see you.
I can not believe it's true.
Come and sit down.
Tell why you have taken quite so.
Alberto, and many like him,
have left their homes.
They hide in the woods, waiting for more.
They have taken a name...
Death Company!
Death company?
It makes me think of evil.
- Who are they?
- Hundreds of young men, Tessa.
They will liberate Milan.
You may soon come home again, sister.
Do you think I can return to Milan?
I think actually.
They are even prepared to die.
Do you fear at Albertos behalf?
Do you love him still?
Yes.
He also loves me.
He wants to marry me...
- I saw...
- Do not worry about your visions.
Listen to your heart.
What you do.
Tell him that your answer is yes.
Then one of us happy in the slightest.
Eleonora!
Take him!
It's a woman! She is armed!
What are you doing here?
Give me the knife.
Come here with the knife!
We are Death's company,
and we become more and more.
- What are you doing here?
- I was on my way home.
- Milan lies in that direction.
- And then what?
Let us be in peace.
Listen carefully.
We will soon be forced to go
to war against Barbarossa.
Many of us will die.
Marry me.
Now...
Do not try to escape.
Why do you understand it?
The world we grew up in,
no longer exists.
Everything has changed. Alt.
I love you.
Shut up!
Shut up, we must retrieve it,
belonging to the emperor!
This is a monastery.
They have no right to come here.
Shut up. Emperors Frederick
has given me the right.
- Do not enter!
- Shut up!
What?
Have I done something wrong?
Hurry.
- What say you?
- It can be funny.
- Look everywhere!
- What is it, sister?
Everywhere!
They resemble each other.
Underwear can hide beautiful women.
Abbess...
How are you?
- Abbess!
- I'm here.
Ask them to unveil.
In God's name...
What you ask is a sacrilege.
- Otherwise, I do it myself.
- Kill me if you will.
- Do not ask me about such things.
- As you will...
Shall we start with that?
It does not seem to be of
a particularly high quality.
It was not so bad.
She would look good with long hair.
What about her?
See.
No.
Her?
She is incredibly beautiful!
Tessa?
Is that you, Tessa?
I've asked for that to happen.
What do you want me to do?
I can do anything.
Stop her!
No, do not do it!
Tessa!
No, no, no...
Don't do it, Tessa.
I beg you!
No, don't do it! I beg you.
I love you.
I love you with all my heart.
I've never loved anyone
so much as I love you.
Stay with me.
I can change me.
I do everything you ask me.
No, I beg you!
Do not leave me.
No!
I ask you...
Give me your hand.
No!
Tessa!
I loved her.
She cut his throat!
- Touch her not!
- So you pay for.
We get burnt on a bonfire!
- Alberto!
- What is it, Nicola?
Eleonora killed nearly Barozzi!
- Where is she?
- On the way to Barbarossa in Alessandria.
They burn her on a bonfire!
Alberto!
Let me go!
Barozzi want you to come
so they can kill you!
- Hold her!
- Do not touch me!
Do not touch me! Damn you!
Let me go!
Get out!
Get out of here!
- Who is it?
- A witch. She just arrived.
In you go, you witch!
I survived.
I do not think you will.
I must look at when you burn.
Bad news...
We've tried to take the city
for several weeks. How's the tunnel?
We dig only in the fighting to hide the sound
And the rain makes it better.
- Grave twice as much.
- The rivers are filled to bursting.
If it rains more, the whole city flooded.
Our men are tired,
and the rain ruining it for us.
Shut up!
We take the city before sunrise.
Make sure the tunnel is finished there.
- They must not be worried.
- I'm not worried.
Yes, she is here now.
She is here.
- Shut up.
- Your Highness...
- It's an order!
- Do as she says.
Close the door.
Do you know who I am?
You must be a very important person.
They give the guards orders.
I want to see the woman who dared to cut
the throats of the emperor's messenger.
Next time I do it properly.
There will be no next time.
You know very well.
Tell me...
Why did you do it?
He killed my sister...
And my husband are risking
their lives because of him.
What do you mean?
In what way?
What happened to your arm?
I was struck by lightning.
Deaths do not it?
Who are you?
Are you a witch?
A witch! Let me out!
Let me out!
Open the door and shut me out!
She's a witch!
I would not be here!
- Let me out!
- Shut up! Get in there!
They have no chance.
swords are in the perfect height.
Well done, everybody.
Hurry!
Be quiet!
Get ready.
Besides all together!
Germans have built a tunnel!
We have been revealed!
The tunnel is closed.
Light the war machines.
We pull us back.
Alessandria damned!
We draw us back to Pavia.
They are loyal to us.
We can stay there for a while.
They will communicate it
to their cousin, Leo Henry.
We need new people.
He must help you.
Henry wants more land. We have been
away from Germany for a long time.
It was a good idea.
I'm starting to pack.
One more thing before we leave.
Pardon the convict from Milan.
Why do you worry about a peasant woman?
She has incredible strength, Frederick.
They say that she is a witch.
She has a scar on her arm
since she was hit by lightning.
- What is it that weighs on you?
- She survived lightning.
Challenge no heaven.
They may pardon her.
She can bring you accidentally
If you burn her.
Beatrix...We must punish her.
If we burn her, it is for her sake.
Be prepared.
How's it going, cousin?
Where is the army which they promised?
Look at me, Your Majesty.
I am 46 years old and has hurt everywhere.
I can not afford to fight anymore.
I am much older than you,
but I will fight for the empire.
I will also, Your Majesty.
Here's some money that goes to many men.
- It's my contribution.
- Stop it!
You know very well that the emperor
doesn't need money, but an army.
They should be ashamed of you!
They were Saxony and Bavaria,
and he protected you from Prince's coup.
Now that the emperor would ask you for help...
You give him nothing but a mere trifle.
What audacity!
Your wife sounds like a man, Frederick.
They are called the Lion...
But you worthless.
Now we are riding on!
Stop complaining, you witch!
- They had to go wait for me!
- It was the Empress's order.
It does not matter as long as
she gets burned to death.
Burn!
Death Company!
We are gathered here today
because we have a common dream.
We dream of liberty.
We have been robbed of our freedom.
They robbed us our freedom to manipulate us...
Divide us up...
And know that our idle fears.
Our common dream can unite us.
We can reclaim our land and
our families can live in peace!
Let us not fear for tomorrow.
To have a day of freedom is worth
more than a hundred days of slavery!
Together we must fight for our freedom.
Freedom!
Stop!
Attack!
See...
It is Lombards.
You too compassionate end!
What the heck?
Keep your positions.
They have seen our Army
and dare not go on the attack.
It's not good.
Your Highness...
The Milanese army is about
three kilometers away.
- Can you see them?
- Milanese, are very stupid.
We can handle them.
It was only the cavalry, who attacked.
The infantry is not in sight.
When we paralyze cavalry...
Infantry will fall apart.
I thank God every night that
he has given me a woman like you.
- My place is with you, your grace.
- No, your place is with the children.
Take the empress with the Pavia!
We are going to war, my love.
Attack!
Keep your positions.
Stay where you are.
Wait, not yet.
Wait!
Not yet!
Now!
Faster!
Go on the attack!
Attack! Ride forward!
What is this?
Up with the swords!
Continue forward!
Forward! Continue forward!
Attack!
Forward!
You there!
No!
Lorenzo!
Now you need to make
your corporate whore of hell!
Look at me!
You should see me when you die.
- Kill me!
- You like!
I have suffered greatly because of you!
- My family!
- I have money!
And my people!
- Kill me. I beg you.
- I do this for Tessa.
Can you feel it?
I do this for my brothers!
This...Look at me!
I do this for my wife!
Look at me!
Do devil take you!
Alberto!
- Alberto...It is the emperor's horse.
- Yes. I can see.
- Where is he?
- He must be here somewhere.
- How should it be.
- I want to see the body.
Barbarossa is dead.
Give me the dagger.
I miss her.
You can not get Eleonora back.
If she were here she would see you happy.
You have achieved what you wanted.
The people got their freedom back.
Look!
Are you here?
You live...
You live!
Alberto...
- What are you doing here?
- Empress saved my life.
They burned another woman in my place.
You live!
I love you.
Freedom.
- Freedom!
Freedom!